export const TigerQuiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'The Sumatran tiger is native to which region?',
    options: ['Sumatra', 'Borneo', 'Malaysia', 'Indonesia'],
    answer: 'Sumatra',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      'What is the primary habitat of the Bengal tiger in the Sundarbans?',
    options: ['Mangrove forests ', 'Grasslands', 'Snowy mountains', 'Deserts'],
    answer: 'Mangrove forests',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'The South China tiger is considered...',
    options: [
      'Critically endangered in the wild',
      'The largest tiger subspecies',
      'Adapted to mountain regions',
      'Increasing in population',
    ],
    answer: 'Critically endangered in the wild',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      'Which tiger subspecies is known for its small size and adaptations to dense forests?',
    options: [
      'Malayan Tiger',
      'Sumatran Tiger',
      'Siberian Tiger',
      'Bengal Tiger',
    ],
    answer: 'Sumatran Tiger',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'The Colossus of Rhodes was located in...',
    options: ['Turkey', 'Crete', 'Rhodes', 'Athens'],
    answer: 'Rhodes',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'How many wild Siberian tigers are estimated to exist today?',
    options: ['Less than 200', 'About 500', 'Over 1,000', 'Approximately 700'],
    answer: 'About 500',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'Which subspecies is found in Malaysia?',
    options: [
      'Sumatran Tiger',
      'Malayan Tiger',
      'South China Tiger',
      'Bengal Tiger',
    ],
    answer: 'Malayan Tiger',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'The main threat to the Sundarbans tiger population is...',
    options: [
      'Rising sea levels',
      'Snowstorms',
      'Overpopulation of prey',
      'Urbanization',
    ],
    answer: 'Rising sea levels',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'What unique skill do Sundarbans tigers possess?',
    options: [
      'Flying short distances',
      'Swimming long distances',
      'Climbing steep cliffs',
      'Digging deep burrows',
    ],
    answer: 'Swimming long distances',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'The South China tiger is currently being rewilded in which country?',
    options: ['South Korea', 'South Africa', 'Australia', 'China'],
    answer: 'South Africa',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Why are Sumatran tigers critically endangered?',
    options: [
      'Excessive hunting for their bones',
      'Habitat loss from palm oil plantations',
      'Lack of prey species',
      'Disease outbreaks',
    ],
    answer: 'Habitat loss from palm oil plantations',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'What is the purpose of tiger patrols in Sumatra?',
    options: [
      'To photograph tigers',
      'To prevent illegal poaching',
      'To count tiger tracks',
      'To guide tourists',
    ],
    answer: 'To prevent illegal poaching',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'What cultural symbol does the Malayan tiger represent?',
    options: [
      'Power and royalty',
      'Peace and harmony',
      'Wealth and prosperity',
      'Knowledge and wisdom',
    ],
    answer: 'Power and royalty',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Which tiger subspecies is the smallest in size?',
    options: [
      'Bengal Tiger',
      'South China Tiger',
      'Sumatran Tiger',
      'Malayan Tiger',
    ],
    answer: 'Sumatran Tiger',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'What tool is used to monitor tiger movements in the wild?',
    options: ['Camera traps', 'Drones', 'Thermal sensors', 'Microchips'],
    answer: 'Camera traps',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      'Which tiger subspecies primarily lives in fragmented forest habitats?',
    options: [
      'Siberian Tiger',
      'Sumatran Tiger',
      'Bengal Tiger',
      'South China Tiger',
    ],
    answer: 'Sumatran Tiger',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      'What is the estimated number of Malayan tigers left in the wild?',
    options: ['300-400', 'Less than 200', '500-700', 'Over 1,000'],
    answer: 'Less than 200',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "The main cause of South China tiger's decline is...",
    options: [
      'Climate change',
      'Hunting and habitat loss',
      'Competition with other predators',
      'Lack of genetic diversity',
    ],
    answer: 'Hunting and habitat loss',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "How long is the Siberian tiger's average territory range?",
    options: [
      '50 square kilometers',
      '100 square kilometers',
      'Over 1,000 square kilometers',
      '500 square kilometers',
    ],
    answer: 'Over 1,000 square kilometers',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'What is the primary prey species for tigers?',
    options: ['Deer', 'Elephants', 'Monkeys', 'Cattle'],
    answer: 'Deer',
  },
];
